Duane Spencer Hatch Collection 1912-1982, (bulk 1940-1982)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series V: Oversized Materials, 1947-1963; undated
  - Subseries 2: Movie Reels
    - Extra Martandam Footage (real and access DVD), undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Give Us the Earth (real and access DVD), 1947 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Goals No. 2 (real and access DVD), undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Nancy Hatch’s Wedding, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Original Reel for Up From Poverty 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Original Reel for Up From Poverty 2, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Original Reel for Up From Poverty 3, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The Jungle and the Plough (real and access DVD), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - The Jungle and the Plough Copy 2, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - The Mexico Story (real and access DVD), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Up From Poverty (real and access DVD), undated (Box 9, Folder 11)